PARDEEP KUMAR SHUKLA

Operations Team Leader

- **\ +919877074155**
- https://king-gr-yt.github.io/Portfolio/
- ☆ Total Experience: 3 Years 1 Months
- @ Pardeepshukla860@gmail.com
- Chandigarh



SUMMARY

Team Leader experienced in directing activities of workgroups. Develops strategies, provides training, sets goals and obtains team feedback. Excellent interpersonal and communication skills. Big picture focus with excellence in communicating goals and vision to succeed. Problem solver, networker, and consensus builder.

EXPERIENCE

04/2024 - Present

Team Lead - Operations
SBI PAYMENTS PVT LTD

Chandigarh, India

- · Manage the day-to-day operations.
- · Develop and implement standard operating procedures (SOPs) to enhance operational efficiency.
- · Utilize data-driven insights to make informed decisions on resource allocation and workforce optimization.
- Worked closely with the sales team to provide operational support, including managing the POS machine lifecycle (installations, de installations, approvals).

08/2022 - 03/2024

Chandigarh, India

Data Entry Operator

LSR Infracon Private Limited

- · Resolved discrepancies between source documents and computer database records
- · Utilized various software programs including MS Office Suite and specialized applications
- · Identified data entry errors and corrected mistakes to achieve near-perfect accuracy in data sets

08/2021 - 07/2022

Data Entry Operator

Grip Rehabilitation Private Limited

- · Gathered and documented statistical information to generate reports
- · Scanned and stored files and records electronically to reduce paper files and secure data
- · Verified confidential or private client information in adherence to state and federal laws

EDUCATION

Chandigarh, India

09/2018

Jetking Certified Hardware And Networking Engineer
 Jetking Chandigarh

Chandigarh, India

· Note key learnings, experience and skills gained relevant to the job.

05/2017

Class XII

CBSE BOARD

· Year of Passing

05/2015

Class X

Chandigarh, India

Chandigarh, India

CBSE BOARD

· Note key learnings, experience and skills gained relevant to the job.

LANGUAGES

Hindi Native

English Intermediate ••••

Punjabi Intermediate **SKILLS**

Css Data Entry

Excel

Front-end

Github

Html

Microsoft Excel

Ms office

KEY ACHIEVEMENTS



NATIONAL GOA GOLD CUP T20 CRICKET CHAMPIONSHIP

Quarter-Finalist



AAKASH NATIONAL TALENT HUNT EXAM

Participation in Talent Hunt Exam